Hello hello friends welcome to my channel step
today I am going to tell you how you can cancel SSC's hand free
dental insurance you
can cancel any achievements in the updater so guys there are two ways, I will
tell you both the ways, your
cancer will be cancelled, both are online but a
little bit of it is offline, you have to
take out the form and send it by email online, one is
not available online, the other you
can do it, so I will tell you both the ways,
let's first send an email, after going to the mail
we will write in the west mail
please cancel my insurance,
I will write to you in the email, if you
send it from your registered email ID then your
insurance will be cancelled, if it is not yours then I will
tell you another way also, you
can register now you can see below and I will
also give you the i button above, you
can go there and mail your registration,
you will get the description below, now you can
go and update your email in it,
please cancel add
Prudential Life Insurance of New Delhi Corporation  Cancel
your second syringe and my life in this fort,
in the waves, whatever is useless, whatever it is,
how is your slip lane?
Now I will write further, you have to write your name,
you
write your full name, the name which you had given in the policy,
in the insurance policy you have to write
this name, then you have to write your phone number,
take your registered phone number, through this you will get to
know the customer care
about you, who is requesting us to
cancel,
here you will also call on this,
friends, in the subject digit above you have to
write the policy number, the computer
automatically reads the policy number
in the subject, so they get to know, so
you have to write the call number here, you have to
write the police1 shampoo and your policy
number which is in your form,
write it here
and you will get it, it will be available
in the description, you can copy and put their email ID on this,
let's abuse in Remedy,
so this feature was sent to the app, it is a
lifeline, see through live.com, to send this paper  If it is of, then
now I will send you my policy
number. I asked you to write it in the zero subject,
so write Idrish and don't write it here. I told
you to send it too, you should check everything
and I sent it. No, but the sandwich
message box. So friends, you go to the mail like this. It takes
five to ten minutes.
You get a call from them. You will
also get a call from a woman from their side.
Whatever problem you have, the mail will
solve it for you. And your account
problem is not solved through the mail. The woman goes to
send the form. How do I get the form from the business? I will give
you the
pump. You click on it,
download the form, now withdraw the question and appeal. Now
fill in your bank account. All your
records will also be seen in your bank account.
In the reform, let me tell you,
this is a
pre-popularity form in two phones. You
fill it in. You will get the refund after
entering your bank account details. So, I will give it to you. So,
how is it? Let me
give you some information about it and tell you
what you have to do
here.  Bank details are there in all policy cancellation
request change police feature rich look
request for women policy number you
must fill in below name and policy
holder and here application for real look
first you have to fill in bank details bank name
branch name head and account you have to fill in
form I will give you a form to fill in the
link below you can watch pooja's video
till you get new video you
can request me by commenting I will
make a video for you and upload it so
now I am going to tell you how to do it let's
download the form I will give
you by calling you the
money will go to the bank and pay the tax
and I would like to tell you from where to
send this form online it will be sent to you on email
after scanning it fill up
completely and take a photo of it and
send it to the email ID given to you
download the form from here there is such screw
dental clinic and tell us what to do so
next
is insurance
cancellation but I will do it right
here we will see the option I am going to
tell you so come here son how can I
cancel the tender  It is like you will be scared by
clicking on the custom from the website, so
you can do it from here and you
can also do this chilli, if you fill the form then it will be
dericted, friends, if you
can send the form with a courier, Om
Banna, after downloading,
I will give the link of that form below, you can check it there, if you have
not subscribed to my channel
then please ask whatever you want by commenting,
I will tell you, there is
no need to worry, your money will be recorded and
your work will also be done.